Víctor Salgado

Developer

Personal Info

Email

victor.ignacio.salgado2002@gmail.com

Phone

+56957005236

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/v%C3%ADc tor-salgado-4ba2932b3/

Skills

Python

JavaScript

ReactJS

Django

NodeJS

Google cloud platform

Software

Python

JavaScript

Django

NodeJS

ReactJS

Google cloud platform

Languages

English

Spanish

Hobby/Interest

Learning
Programming

ΑI

Professional programmer with expertise in both front-end and back-end development. I possess excellent planning and teamwork skills, enabling me to meet deadlines and achieve optimal results.

I would like to work for a company that supports the professional development of its employees.

Work History

2023-09

Backend developer

- present

Audibots, Las condes

In Audibots I make process automation robots using various languages such as Python, JavaScript, RocketBot, and UIPath.

2022-09

Web developer

- 2023-03

Influénciame, Las condes

Development of various webpages using different frameworks and programming lenguages such as Python, Django, ReactJS, JavaScript,

NodeJS

2020-03

Developer

- present

Freelance, San bernardo

Different projects like:

-Trading bot using Python

-Data analysis webpage using Django and Langchain (AI)

-Creation of evaluations using AI with FastAPI and ReactJS (Vite)

-Mental health webpage using Django and MySQL (ORM)

-License plate recognition using Python

-Webpages for clients

2021-07

Assistant Teacher

- 2021-12

Diego Portales University (UDP), Santiago

I was a teaching assistant at Diego Portales University for programming, in addition to giving private lessons in advanced programming.

2023-01

My GITHUB

- present

Freelance, San Bernardo

https://github.com/Champinhon

Education

2020-03

Software engineer

- 2022-08

Diego Portales University, Santiago

I studied there for 3 years

Courses

2022-05

Web Development Bootcamp

2022-09

Al with Python